Hey everyone, welcome to this video called 5 affordable Finnish goth outfits and I put together some really cool looks with items from Honor Clothing from the UK so you know what to wear when you want to go for a night out in the goth scene or pretty scene.
We're going to have latex outfits, we're going to have PVC and I hope I can give you some ideas for cool outfits. And I also got news. I'm really happy to announce that I'm an official owner-investor from now on.
and that also means you will see more Honor videos on my channel in the next few months
so you can get to know the brand a bit better and see what they have to offer
because I think the product range is really cool.
I own already a lot of pieces so it's a brand that I can really recommend.
By the way this blouse is also from Honor but I'm going to start with the first look now
and I'm going to change into a latex dress.
I'm presenting to you the first outfit. I call it gold and black.
beauty
Because I added obviously gold details to this black dress like a belt
like a choker we have gold here in the boots and
I could also add like a little
bag with golden details and
Be on my way to the next goth party or the next fetish party because it would be suitable for both
The dress itself is a great basic. It's a long sleeve black 0.4mm and it has a zipper that runs until here.
So you can open it and get into it really fast and easy. You just have to use oil to get into the long sleeves.
But as they're not too tight it's also really easy.
And you have so many options with this dress to spice it up.
up. I did it here with the fishnets and all the accessories. You could also wear it with the latex
leggings for example or other tights. You could add a jacket on top of it and you always come back
to having one good basic dress in your closet because that's what you need. And yes you can
close the zipper and have a different look. Let me check in the mirror. Of course I would have
like to get rid of the choker underneath but you get the idea
you could also add a harness
if you close it or add some gloves, it's up to you
next I'm going to show you the bodysuit
also black but different material. Outfit number two is this
bodysuit made of PVC fabric and I think it's the cheapest piece I'm going to show you
today
I paired it again with some black fishnets because I think
PVC and fishnets is really something that always works.
And with this bodysuit we have a belt that comes with the bodysuit.
So this is not an addition but part of the outfit.
Because you also have belt loops here.
Sewn through the bodysuit.
Which makes it look kind of cute.
With the bodysuit you have a lot of styling options.
You can wear it as a top only.
If you put skirt or leggings on top of it.
or you can wear with a jacket for example
like I wanna try with my leather jacket
I think it's always a funny look if you have long sleeves at the upper body
but only tights and a bodysuit on the lower body
so with the jacket is also an option especially if it gets cold
or some colored tights maybe that's also a cool idea or you could add um tights to your arms like
the good old goth people do rip tights everywhere by the way rip tights i also rip mine again
i just can't wear tights without destroying them anyway back to the outfit
It is rather plain. I did not add any accessories because I have the belt here and I want to focus on the belt.
I can also, of course, close the bodysuit.
I think I have some latex shiner.
Or you can also use a bit of latex shiner if you want to shine up your PVC.
That's a good tip.
Yeah, I think that's cool.
look. You can definitely go to a fetish party like that. You could also go to a golf party like that
and it is an affordable outfit. So all the boxes from the title ticked and I'm going to switch into
the next one. Outfit number three, latex again and this time it's a two-piece set, a blouse and a skirt.
Has a completely different vibe than the first latex dress because it is a lot straighter I'd say.
and I paired it with some high heels and I could also pair it with my glasses yes I'm wearing
glasses normally and if I want to dig out all the stereotypes I'm taking this one as well
but we're not here to talk about 30 stereotypes but about cool outfits so I'm giving you some
more details about the blouse you can see it has puffy sleeves which makes the design really stand
out it also has these ruffles here in the bust area okay on this blouse we got the color we got
the pleating here and here we have the snaps and we have decorative seams here and this one with
pleating again so for the price you get a lot of details and a lot of design features and I think
it also goes for skirt I paired it with simple black pencil skirt I'll just put a link to the
on our webpage in the description text because they have a lot of skirts different lengths
different colors different types and you can definitely check them out I mean you could also
pair it with the leggings for example next up I'm going to show you a dress made of a material we
haven't seen today neoprene. Offer number four is this really short black dress made of neoprene
fabric and I do love this fabric because it's so comfortable but it looks so cool and unique
because it's matte so the only matte piece in this video today and it also makes a great body
shape because it works just like shapewear so yay we like that and it runs a bit small I'm
wearing size medium so be careful with that one when it comes to sizing I love the details here
with the cross stitches so it's not just a plain dress and I mean you could wear a jacket on top
or tights underneath it is not the cheapest item in this video but it's also the most unique item
due to the fabric and it is just like a scuba suit with a fabric lining on the
inside. Sadly there aren't that many neoprene items in the honor shops just a
few but this one is my favorite anyway so check it out if you want to have
something new what is not latex or PVC but something unique. I have to repeat
comfy again because that's just what it is. And on to the next outfit now. This is
the final look and it's basically a version of the first look except for this is PVC and I paired it
with silver accessories yeah but for some people who don't like latex or have latex allergy PVC
is a great substitute or alternative and you can style it as well as the latex dress I also added
belt and a choker and again this is a little black dress that is valuable in every closet
and you can get a lot of these great affordable basics. I have this dress for a couple of years
now and I've worn it really often because it's such an easy outfit. I'm wearing size UK 8 by the
way and of course I can also close the zipper like this and it's again a completely different
look you can also detach the belt for a plain look and that was basically it for today
okay tell me in the comments which one was your favorite also check out honor and use my discount
I'll write everything down below in the description text as always leave a
thumbs up and I'll see you in the next video have a nice day bye